const questions = [
    {
        question: "Javascript is an _______ language",
        choice1: "Object-Oriented",
        choice2: "Object-Based",
        choice3: "Procedural",
        choice4: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        choice1: "const",
        choice2: "let",
        choice3: "Both const and let",
        choice4: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
        choice1: "Variables",
        choice2: "Functions",
        choice3: "Objects",
        choice4: "All of the above",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?",
        choice1: "Vue",
        choice2: "React",
        choice3: "Node",
        choice4: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?",
        choice1: "clearTimer",
        choice2: "stopInterval",
        choice3: "clearInterval",
        choice4: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 3
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "How do we write a comment in javascript?",
        choice1: "/**/",
        choice2: "//",
        choice3: "#",
        choice4: "Both /**/ and //",
        correctAnswer: 4
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        choice1: "convert()",
        choice2: "parse()",
        choice3: "stringify()",
        choice4: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 3
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
        choice1: "async",
        choice2: "await",
        choice3: "setTimeout",
        choice4: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 1
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a Logical Operator",
        choice1: "!",
        choice2: "&&",
        choice3: "||",
        choice4: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 4
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "When an operatorâ€™s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
        choice1: "Undefined",
        choice2: "Boolean",
        choice3: "Integer",
        choice4: "Object",
        correctAnswer: 4
    }
];

